All right,
I want to welcome everybody to night
school. We have a bunch of people
popping in, so we're going to give them
a few minutes.
And as everybody pops in here in the
chat, let's write wherever we're coming
in from. So, is it New York? You're in
Austin, Texas, SF, around the world. Let
us know where you're dialing in from.
Now, we have over 400 people signed up
for this session. So, there's going to
be a lot of people all over the place.
So, I'm excited to see Louisiana, New
Zealand. That's the farthest.
We have Orange County, Canada.
Love it.
Now, there's a few people in the room
who are going to be sort of my helpers,
staff members from Gauntlet. you'll see
uh they're going to write with Gauntlet
or from Gauntlet on their display names.
So, help answer some of your questions.
But as you're hopping into this class,
please add where you're dialing in from.
And let's also add why we are joining
this class.
Why are you joining this class on how to
interview as an AI first engineer? I
want to deliver value to you guys. And
so, this is completely live. I'll be
doing a ton of Q&A at the end. So, what
is the reason why you joined the class?
Poland. That's another one.
New Hampshire. All right.
Okay. You don't interview well. Looking
for a better job to get better
understanding.
transitioning from senior writer former
Lambda school.
Yes, the session is going to be recorded
and available on YouTube afterward.
I have an opportunity to join an AI
company. Amazing. McKini, Texas, looking
for a job.
Transitioning from TPM to AI engineer.
Love it. Exploring the AI landscape.
Looking for a better job.
would love to learn more about
experimenting. Don't interview well.
Imposter syndrome, of course.
This is great. The awesome part about
this is
this is going to help me decide what
other classes I should have for night
school. So the whole point of night
scroll is to take the gauntlet AI
curriculum and to ensure that there is
an open version of that curriculum that
all of you can use to get better at
either a technical skill, an
interviewing skill, and just get hired
much faster in this job market. So I'm
excited to see all this inside of the
chat so we can actually see what the
next classes might be. We're going to
give people another minute. We have 109
people already joining us. We're going
to get started here in just a minute and
we'll get started on our session on how
to interview as an AI first engineer.
Someone is saying being an AI engineer
is a completely new role to me and it's
an interesting change for sure. This is
a role that didn't exist 8 months ago,
right? The 8 months ago this role was
completely something that people were
thinking about. HR didn't have a name
for it. All of a sudden, cloud code
reaches a maxima and everybody is
looking for an AI first engineer. And so
I think this is going to be really
insightful for all of you and I'm
excited to get started. Okay, so I want
to go through how night school works.
Night School is a weekly session that we
have here at Gauntlet AI that is open to
the public. And this session is going to
go over either a technical skill, a soft
skill, or something that has to do with
both of those areas when it comes to
getting hired as an AI engineer. We run
a 10-week accelerator, 3 weeks remote, 7
weeks on-site, where all we do is
completely immerse ourselves in AI. That
means I have over a hundred students at
our headquarters right now in Austin,
Texas that are devoting over a thousand
hours to being at the frontier of AI. My
goal is to take that curriculum and
bring it to you for free. So, if you
have questions, if you have uh specific
concerns, if you're wondering about
something, please, please, please add it
to the chat. Here's how Q&A is going to
work. I have three of my Gauntlet staff
members, Derek, Aaron, and Nina, inside
of the chat with you. They're going to
be able to answer your questions on the
fly as I'm teaching. At the end of my
session, I'll be spending about 15 to 30
minutes on Q&A alone. I've also asked
the staff, Sunny and Tom, to highlight
some of the best questions for me. These
best questions are then being
highlighted on my phone here, so I can
actually answer them out loud. So, we're
there's a lot of people in the room, so
we're going to do our best to make sure
all your questions are answered. But
here's what you should do for the next
40 to 45 minutes. Lock in, pay attention
to what I'm trying to say, participate
in some of the exercises, note down your
question in the chat, and we'll have one
of our staff members answer it async or
I'll answer it out loud at the end of
the session. This is exactly how classes
work here at Gauntlet AI. We take a
portion of the class and have it focused
on the lecture material. Once the
lecture material is over, we usually
have a Q&A session for about 15 to 30
minutes and then an exercise at the end
that individuals can do to sort of get
prepared and take themselves to the next
level. That's exactly what we'll be
doing today.
All right.
Today's class is going to be on how to
interview as an AI first engineer. The
reason why I think I can talk about this
is because I've partnered with over 81
companies and teams. I've trained over a
thousand engineers over the last two
years and I've placed over 300 gauntlet
grads as AI first engineers. We partner
with organizations like
GoFundMe, Zapier, Nerdy, Nexa, and my
graduates are becoming AI first
engineers at all of these organizations.
Our goal here at Gauntlet is to train
the next generation of engineers,
leaders, managers, and business owners
to be AI first across the board. That is
why I can come to you and say I
understand how people are trying to hire
for these AI roles. I've talked to CTO's
across the board. I've hired personally
as a CTO and the system is entirely
broken. This is real data from a job
posting that I recently had where 88% of
all of the applications I got were AI
generated resumes. You could tell by how
exact the keywords were being used. You
could tell by how precise everything
matched my job description. You can tell
that it's just really hard to find
signal in a sea of noise. There is so
much noise out there where people are
claiming overexaggerating and not
actually talking to the exact skill set
that they have. When you actually start
talking to these people and you start
interviewing them, you realize, hey, he
doesn't actually have the knowledge for
this specific position or no, they did
something similar, but it's not exactly
what I'm looking for. Based on that job
posting, I had 88% which I thought were
AI generated résumés. I saw identical
keywords for about 76% of that uh those
applications. About 12% in my opinion
were like, "Okay, this guy's probably
good. He has a brand name. He has a
referral. There's some signal here that
makes it me seem like, hey, this is
actually a valid candidate." And then
finally, about 8% did move on to the
interview round. That is what's
happening on this side of the hiring
cycle. Let's say you're a CTO. Let's say
you're an engineering manager. Let's say
you're uh a product leader. It doesn't
matter what area this is happening in
in, but where what what what's happening
is we're getting 10,000 AI generated
applications. There's like a another
agent coming out that is doing job
search for you and then uploading your
apps. And we we have little to no way to
discern signal from noise. And so I this
is important because this signal is
broken. We are then going to referrals
and we're going to brand names and we're
going to test and we're going to other
in-person events, conferences, college
meetups, and we're trying to find our
engineers in that location. Now, what
happens when you do that virtual
interview? Everybody's using some sort
of coding assistant on the right side.
They have some sort of hidden earpiece.
There's like a screen overlay app that
we've heard of like eight of them now.
They there's also these like ghost
riding co-pilots. It's really hard to
discern even in the interview if this
person actually knows what they're
talking about. That is to the point
where I have individuals come into my
headquarters now and interview because I
have better signal watching them in
person, talking to them directly than I
do over some sort of virtual meeting.
That is the state of the market. And
everything is becoming a knowledge
round. Meaning if we know that AI can
generate code, if we know that AI is
able to do XYZ portion of the entire
software development life cycle, then
what part becomes important? Judgment,
taste, the ability to decide when to do
what with your AI is the key skill.
There's two tracks that I want you to
focus in on. And these two tracks
correspond with the gauntlet curriculum.
The gauntlet curriculum focuses on
coding with AI and building AI
applications. Now, coding with AI means
you have codecs, claude code, open code,
whatever you've decided your harness is
for coding, you have a methodology on
top by which you code with that harness.
I'll give you an example of this.
Currently, I use claude code as my
primary harness. Claude code uses uh
linear as a task management tool. I use
plan mode on cloud code. I have a
testing suite with three other sub aents
and then I do code review with reptile.
That is my AI first methodology. I've
taken three or four tools, four or five
skills and the exact steps from start to
finish to better understand how to
actually code with AI. I want to make
sure that as I'm coding, I can outline
and talk about this methodology step by
step. I have seen inside of interviews
for both gauntlet students and for
individuals that are interviewing across
the board here in Austin, Texas, that
people are asked directly, how do you
use cloud code? What skills are you
using? How are you manipulating these
skills? How are you automating the
things like code review and deployment?
What is a plug-in? Are you using a
plug-in for deployment? These are
important questions to discern if you
actually know what you're doing. When it
comes to using coding agents, there's
there's dabbling and there's actually
understanding something. I would
encourage all of you to actually put in
the time. Spend 20 to 40 hours with your
coding agent of choice. Understand the
nuances, understand the prompting,
understand the skills, understand the
exact methodology before you start
thinking about your methodology. The
other part is building AI applications.
If you were to take all of the big AI
applications in the market right now,
they all come down to four primitives
and I think people complicate this a
lot, but the four primitives are rag,
agents, graphs, and evals. Now, each of
these topics is going to be key because
when you're interviewing to be an AI
engineer, these are the questions that
you might get. What's agentic rag?
What's metadata filtered rag? What
vector database are you using for your
rag system? Where do where do rag
systems work and where do they break?
What's an agent? What's the difference
between an agent and a graph? Uh what's
an eval? Why are you scoring something?
What's LLM as a judge? What's an
observability platform? Questions like
these are exactly what you should be
exposed to and be working with to be
even in the arena to be hired as an AI
first engineer. The most important part
about this is you need to have one, two,
three tools in each of these categories.
You don't need to go crazy. One of the
biggest things that happens in AI is
there's a new discovery or something
comes out every single day and we think
that the breadth of what we learn is
important. When it's not the breath, it
is the depth. Meaning you need to go
deeper into lang chain, deeper into claw
SDK, deeper into lang. You need to pick
your tool set and stick with it. Okay.
So those are the two areas that you
should be ramping up on. And this is
exactly what Gauntlet focuses on in
terms of our curriculum.
Now, when you when I talk about coding
with AI, I talked about a methodology,
but I also want to give you specific
things I would focus on for practicing
during the interview and what you might
be asked to do. Walk me through your
cloud code workflow step by step. To
some people, this might be like, hey,
this is a stupid question. My cla code
workflow is just answering and prompting
and, you know, answering whatever I have
to answer or giving the information I
need to give or connecting something.
It's pretty straight and simple.
That shows that you are a novice.
If you truly have a cloud code workflow,
you should have one for green field
projects and brownfield projects. You
should understand how your cloud code
orchestrator is taking in all of the
context and the data. You should
understand how what your testing
strategy is, your code review strategy
is, what model you're using when. That
all makes up your methodology. The first
week of Gauntlet, we tell everybody,
hey,
there's no manual coding for the next
two weeks. Your goal is to build an AI
first methodology, which means that you
and your coding agent should be in a
symbiosis be able to code and work with
each other perfectly. So when someone
tells you, "Walk me through your cloud
code workflow," you should be able to
say, "I start off with doing meetings
across the team, the product manager,
the UX designer, across whoever's
designated as a subject matter expert,
and I do interviews. I use granola to
take down every single thing that
they're saying, and I make sure that I
understand exactly what the ticket
requires. Once I have all of this
information, I'm taking all my granola
notes. I'm taking the ticket from Jira
and I've connected the MCP servers
across both of those different tools.
I'm bringing in all this information
into cloud code inside of an MD file.
Then I turn on plan mode inside of Cloud
Code where I am walking through the
exact implementation process, the
directories that are going to be
updated, the exact code that I'm going
to write through, and I'm using voice
dictation through Aqua to do so. After I
do that, I'm going to walk through and
start implementing a task list where
I'll create a simple MD file with all a
checklist of all the things that have to
be completed plus phases that I can uh
walk in and see if everything is working
perfectly. Once I have that, then I can
go step by step by step and actually
ship that piece of code. That is a
methodology.
It is a string of connected tools that
you know exactly how to use well so that
you can get the code on the other side
properly. You should be able to convey
this in an interview if you want to be
an AI first engineer. Now there's three
other areas that I think are super
important. One of them is how do you
manage task? If you have so many things
that are happening within an entire
coding workflow, one of the key
questions you'll get inside of the
interview is are you using linear? Are
you using a task management platform? Is
there something that you're doing
specifically to manage these task?
Skills are by far one of the most
important things that you could be doing
and they are available across all of the
coding agents whether it's cursor, codec
or cloud code. A skill is essentially
taking domain expertise from whichever
area of the company that you're working
in. Putting that domain expertise in a
single file that claude code can then
progressively disclose to the context
window is exactly one of the key ways of
making your coding strategy or coding
methodologies 10 times better. So if you
have not tried any skills yet knowing
and h knowing what a skill is and how to
use it is super important.
All right, next one is staying in
control. Now, one of the key areas that
we try to build credibility in an
interview, and I do this myself, and
this could be with even some of the
hiring partners here at Gauntlet AI, for
example, Mark from Replicated, for
example, um I don't know, all the CTOs
that we're talking to, they're asking
this one question. How do you verify AI
generated code before it ships? That
might be building a test suite. That
might be having a code review sub agent.
That might be ensuring that each of the
things follow a certain skill that
identifies and outlines engineering
standards. Verification is going to be
the first question you get when you try
to get an AI engineer job. They want to
make sure that you have the underlying
experience and skill set as a software
engineer already, but you can also be a
stop gap to AI going off the rails. A
nice analogy uh that I've heard before
is before we used to be the actors in a
movie when we were building software,
but now we're the director of those
actors. Each of these agents can go in
multiple different directions. And we
want to see inside of the interview that
you're able to actually know exactly
when AI is correct, when AI is wrong,
when AI is partially right, when AI
needs to be directionally turned around.
That is going to be one of the questions
you get in your interview no matter
what. Now, the other thing that happens
when you're using a ton of AI on top of
your codebase is that you lose track of
your codebase as AI keeps adding code,
keeps adding code, keeps adding code.
Once you start losing track of that
codebase and you're not understanding
what each directory is doing, what each
file is doing, what all the different
agents, all the different endpoints, all
the different software that you've
created is doing, then that is a red
flag. I'm not saying that you need to
understand every single line of code.
What I'm trying to tell you is you need
to understand at the directory level
what each part of your codebase is
doing, why you've used certain
dependencies, what this class is doing,
what this endpoint is doing, what the
goal of what you're trying to build is.
What happens is we try to vibe code so
much that we lose complete control of
our codebase. If that becomes what is
happening, then you are not an AI
engineer. You're just letting go of the
reins.
Now the other thing is as engineers
there's so many things that we know
already that we want to make our code as
simple as possible. We want to ensure
that there's no dead code. We want to
have comments on our code. We want to be
able to review the code in a really nice
way. You should still keep all of those
things intact. Your comment structure,
your testing strategy, your code review
methodology, your ability to say that,
hey, I have this exact methodology or
engineering standard from what I'm
building. and keeping those set, keeping
those intact is key. So, what are we
looking for when we're asking you this
question? We're trying to discern if you
actually know how to wield your coding
agent well or not. We're trying to see
if you're losing control of your
codebase or you know when to stop AI or
when to let AI go. We're trying to check
and see if you actually understand the
code that you're generating. We're
trying to see if the code that you're
generating can be verified and you have
actual system by which you're doing so.
This whole thing is your AI first
development methodology and that is
going to be tested in an interview no
matter what.
Okay. Now when you're building AI there
are four pillars. Now people will say
hey why don't you add fine-tuning or
reinforcement learning or classical
learning. That is important, don't get
me wrong. But if you're a software
engineering, if you're a software
engineer, excuse me, building at the
application level, then these are the
four pillars by which you should focus.
Rag, graphs, agents, evals. By far the
thing that people forget always is eval
because they don't think it's important.
Right now, every single thing that you
see in the market, whether it's claude
code agent harness, whether it's some of
the graph-based agents across banking
systems, whether it's a customer support
agent, whether it's manis, everything is
based off of these four primitives and
they are the foundations of everything
that is being built. Rag or retrieval,
which means how can you grab context
whenever you need it. How can you
reliably get context from a vector
database from structured context from a
SQL database? Context across documents,
context across different areas of your
codebase. That is what rag is. It's
retrieval. Adding it to your context
window and then being able to have a
better output. A graph. A graph is nodes
and edges that can go in multiple
different directions and simulate well
how an agent would act across let's say
8 9 10 pathways. When you have a regular
agent, that regular agent can act in a
million different ways. But what a graph
lets you do is have guardrails across
all the different ways an agent can act.
That means you start by building a
graph. That graph gets better and better
and better over time. you understand all
the different areas where a graph should
be performing and you can then turn it
into an agent. An agent is going to be a
single orchestrator with multiple
skills, multiple connectors, MCP API
connections that the agent is able to
then orchestrate over 20 tools to
actually do something to actually make
up new sequences of work and workflows
that complete task end to end. And
finally, eval. Evals are the scoring
system which let us know if the last
three foundations are actually working
well or not. Right? A lot of people love
to have demos. I was working with this
team who was building a website builder
on top of their application and they had
this website builder running for about 6
months but they had no idea if it was
even leading to any conversion. We set
up a complete eval suite which tracked
if a human would actually move from
joining the website all the way to
converting and converting to a premium
account. We mapped it out step by step
with checkpoints and then we able to see
the evals and how people move through
that funnel. That is what you need. The
ability to score the performance, the
ability to see traction on top of your
application using actual numerical data.
These EVOs become by far one of the most
important things you can do to get
started in AI. So these four topics
you're going to get asked about inside
of your interview no matter what. So if
you don't know anything about them,
that's totally fine. There's YouTube
University and YouTube University has so
many videos across all four of these
topic areas.
Now, eval is what separates everybody
from being a true engineer or from
somebody that's just kind of dabbling.
What is an eval set? How do you build
one? That's a question you'll be asked.
There's how do you run experiments on
top of different models? If you have an
agent, can you manipulate which model
you're using, run your eval suite, and
then as a result see which model
performs best? What is observability?
What are observability platforms? How do
you connect to an observability platform
and actually use one? And then what are
the different ways you can use
observability to see what's working well
and what's working? What's not working
well? What's Langmith? What's Langfuse?
What are what's a good eval pipeline
look like? When I look at candidates,
there's people who can prompt. That's
basically everybody. Everybody at this
point can prompt. Then there's people
who can measure. That means they
understand how to actually connect an
observability platform that they
actually understand that there should be
some sort of measurement and what to
measure. And then finally, there's
people who can improve agentic systems.
So if you've set up your agent, if
you've set up your chatbot, if you've
set up your rag pipeline, you should be
able to iterate on it and improve it
over time. That is the gold standard
when deciding who is a true AI engineer
and who isn't.
Now, this is going to be some of like
the key topics in gauntlet week 3, four,
five where it's important for you to do
complete projects. If you decide to
build a rag system, add emails to it. If
you decide to build a graph for an
agent, add emails to it. walk through
your methodology for testing that system
and then improving that system over
time.
Okay, so this is the interview arc. This
is what's going to happen in your AI
interview. Uh AI first interview. Uh I
think we'll have AI interviews sometime
soon probably as well. Fun fact, we use
AI interviewers in Gauntlet for grading.
Okay, so the interview arc is they're
going to start with a credibility check.
It's going to be hypers specific
questions and edge cases on top of the
tech stacks that you have experience in.
This is not going to be like lead code.
This is not going to be like some of the
questions that we used were used to
getting in the old software engineering
life cycle. It's going to be like hey
you have experience in node tell me
about MVM. You have experience in Python
tell me how to port C into Python. I'm
not sure. Right. Decide what exactly is
going to be the knowledge base or the
foundation that certifies that your
experience in a tech stack is valid.
Those questions are going to be asked to
you. These questions can be generated by
AI really well. You can go into AI say
that hey I'm going to be interviewing
for X Y andZ position as an AI first
engineer. I'm going to have Python and
Java as the two things that they ask me
about and can you generate some
questions for me. Saying those questions
out loud, answering them really well is
going to be important. So, that's going
to be the first approach that these u
managers take to deciding if you're
worth it for the job. The next part
they're going to talk about probing how
deep your knowledge is of software
engineering. Software engineering is not
just coding. One of my first mentors
told me that there's coding and then
there's actually software engineering
because software engineering has
security, has deployment, has
scalability. All of these things are
things that you're going to be asked
about. If coding agents have pretty much
taken over the generation
portion of the software development life
cycle, there's seven other areas that
you can focus in on. Maybe that's task
generation. Maybe that's uh scaffolding
a repository. Maybe that's deployment.
Maybe that's security. Maybe that's
scaling this across your cloud
infrastructure. These are questions
you're going to get no matter what. So
you need to first have some sort of
credibility check to make sure that your
knowledge of a tech stack is valid. You
need to have the ability to talk about
the full software development life
cycle. Meaning that hey, I can talk
about security, I can talk about
scalability, and I can talk about
deployment. Finally, you need to have
some set level of product sense.
Gauntlet believes that as we get closer
and closer to coding being dominated by
AI, product manager and engineer are
becoming the same profession. I have
worked with teams that are making
product manager and engineer the same
position and calling it an AI first
builder. There's another company calling
it a full stack builder. Having a little
bit of product sense, understanding what
the user wants, actually understanding
the intent of a ticket, making sure that
the user is able to discern what is
supposed to happen with this feature is
going to be important. In the past, as
an engineer, it was required less of you
to understand exactly what the user
wanted. You you needed to be involved in
user reviews much less. Now, it is a
part about a part of what you're doing.
It is going to be important to discern
uh that skill inside of your interview
so the manager feels like hey this guy
actually understands a little bit of
product. He knows what decision to make
when. He has good judgment when it comes
to users. As a result, this can be a
better product on the other side.
Finally, workflow openness. What do I
mean by this? All right, there are some
people who say they are AI first when
they're truly not.
There's a bunch of people out there who
don't believe that AI should be involved
in work at all. There's individuals who
kind of embrace it but kind of don't.
There's individuals who have a ton of
reservations. There's individuals who
have a ton of preconceived notions.
That's fine. You can believe what you
want to believe, but when you go into an
interview, they're 100% going to check
how open are you to adopting a new way
of work. In the era of AI, the way we
work is fundamentally changing. And if
the way we work is fundamentally
changing then you should be open and
adaptable to whatever that may be. Now
there it could be specri development it
could be something else right but the
goal here is are you open to changing
the way you've been doing things
okay to how to pass the credibility
check is to have projects that can speak
to your experience. These could be
deployed work this could be complete
work at the that you've done across your
experience. You need to have the ability
to open up that app inside of your
portfolio, go under the hood, articulate
maybe how AI helped you build what you
just built, if it did, and describe any
of the bugs it may have, the trade-offs
you made, and then the judgment you had
when building the application. You want
to make sure that you are the engineer,
AI is the tool, and that's it. One more
time. You are the engineer. AI is the
tool. And what you're trying to show is
that you can wield your tool
the best compared to whoever else is
interviewing.
Now, product sense in the era, AI era,
just means that you have good judgment.
That means that if let's say you were
bottlenecked for 2 weeks and you had a
bunch of tickets to do, you would know
what ticket to focus on. Maybe you would
use AI to take in all of the user
interviews to better understand exactly
what was going on to pick the right
ticket to work on. Maybe you'd be better
able to prioritize which features would
drive more user adoption than other
features. This level of judgment is what
people are looking for. That doesn't
mean that you have to completely go out
and be a product manager. That means you
need to have a certain level of taste
and judgment to decide what ticket is
more important. How should I approach
this ticket? How can I thoughtfully make
sure that we account for X, Y, and Z
scenarios? What's the trade-off between
doing this ticket and doing that ticket?
What's the trade-off in this approach
and that approach? This architecture and
that architecture. That level of
judgment you should have going to the
interview.
Now, workflow openness is what I talked
about earlier. And I think this diagram
illustrates properly what I'm talking
about. there's too resistant, which just
means I'm never going to adopt AI at
all. Or they might come off as, hey, I'm
going to adopt AI just to like
autocomplete, but I'm never going to
actually let it take take over my
workflow. Then on the other side, we
have, hey, I'm going to vibe code
everything. I'm going to generate a
million lines of code, not review it at
all, not have testing suites, and
actually go down the line and just ship
as much as I can. I think the right
answer is in the middle. Right. And I
think as AI gets better and better and
better, AI will become our digital
coworker. But until it gets there, we
need to have good verification systems
to ensure that this is a methodology.
This is leverage being given to me as an
engineer and it's going to introduce
some risk and my goal should be to
mitigate that risk. The director of this
movie, I need to make sure that the
actors are in the right location.
Okay, so this is what we're looking for
uh to give you a sort of breakdown of
all the skills. If you were to go into
an AI first engineer interview right
now, you want to be able to code with
AI, understand methodology, understand
plan mode, what skills are, task
management. You need to have some sort
of verification strategy. Could be
testing suites, could be manual review,
code review, sub aents, whatever that
philosophy is. You need to understand
the primitives, rag, agents, graphs,
evals. And then you need to have some
level of product sense. Talk about
trade-offs, prioritization, comms across
the entire team. When you're thinking
about preparing for an interview as an
AI first engineer, these are also the
areas that you should get really good
at. I'm not saying you need to be
perfect and handle all edge cases, but
if you had to figure out what are the
key areas of focus, this is what I would
focus on.
Okay?
So, we are about 35 minutes in.
What I'm going to start doing now is
we're going to do a few practice rounds
together. I don't believe in completely
theoretical lectures. That's not who I
am. The goal here is I want you guys I'm
going to give you a question from the
list and inside of the chat I'm going to
ask you to answer that question as you
would based on the experience you have
and as if you're inside of an interview.
If you have a dictation app, I use Aqua
for example, you can use the dictation
app to just answer your question and add
it to the Zoom chat. But I'm gonna pick
question number five. Tell me about a
time AI gave you bad code. How did you
catch it?
So the question posed to you, act like
this is a real interview. Tell me about
a time AI gave you bad code. How did you
catch it?
Integration tests are good. Type check.
Bang on. Unit test.
I did manual Q&A of the feature and I
asked it to build and it did work
properly. Good.
Some through unit test
unconnected AI triggers.
I use TDD. Great. And eval. Well done.
Terraform code created by AI. I was
building a multiplayer game and the back
end needed to hide information from one
player and the others asked a change.
Okay.
With my project, I caught a PR.
I also keep the output small so I can
see it all. Nice. I made sure to run
test to see if everything was working.
AI gave me bad code
visibility
mythos. Yeah, exactly.
Bad separation. Test the output.
Okay. Not bad. Not bad at all. Keep
going. I'm going to give you my answer
because I think it's important. I think
what I'm looking for when I ask this
question in an interview is the
following.
I actually broke up the exact tasks that
claude code was supposed to do into
phases. Each of the phases had
acceptance criteria. This acceptance
criteria was either a playright test,
integration test, end to end test, a
unit test, and maybe some things I could
check manually on the deployed
application. I had already deployed the
application earlier and what I was doing
is deploying it to a dev branch so I can
actually see and test out what I was
building. As Claude code would go
through each of the phases, I would
check the acceptance criteria, I would
go into the dev branch and actually see
what was breaking, what was working, and
then I would run the test manually
because Cloud Code likes to lie about
test passing all the time. And I would
make sure that those tests were actually
passing. This is exactly what happened
when I was building the Gauntlet AI LMS.
The LMS had this one bug where it was
unable to showcase all the scheduled
classes in a single calendar view. I
found that bug and AI kept telling me
no, it was working. I was able to do
that through my acceptance criteria, the
fact that I broke down the entire task
into phases, the test suite that I had,
and by reviewing the output myself.
Okay, what did I include in my answer? I
included a walkthrough of my
methodology. I included exactly what I
would do in a specific scenario. And I
included an example of something I was
actually building that if I was asked to
showcase, I can open up the GitHub
repository and talk about. That is what
you need to do out loud. Now, one of the
things we have here at Gauntlet is we
have an AI interviewer and each of the
students is forced to actually input
uh like a video of them walking through
their project for their submission every
single week. And the goal here is you
should act like it's a real interview.
Your goal should be that hey, I'm
talking to my future interviewer and I'm
going to walk through X, Y, and Z the
way I would for that specific project.
Now, if that's the case, then everything
we do with the questions I'm giving you
right now, you need to be able to take
that question, answer it out loud, even
record yourself, and then see how you
perform. Okay, next one. Building with
AI. Now, many of you may not have
actually started learning about some of
these primitives of AI. There are a
bunch of resources that you can go out
and find. The gauntlet cohort focuses on
this in the first two weeks of our
program where we talk about rag, graphs,
agents, and evals. But the goal here
should be how can I take some of the
specific questions I may be asked in
these areas and then be able to answer
them really well out loud. So, back in
the chat, I want everybody to see if
they can answer question number six.
What does observability mean in an LLM
application?
Also, I'm seeing a ton of questions
about Gauntlet AI. If that's the case,
you can go to gauntletai.comfaq.
You can see all of our questions that
our little agent can answer for you
there. That's gauntletai.comfaq.
All right. Observability means that you
can trace the decision all the way
through. Observability means that you
have the ability to see the reasoning
and the agents and its tool calls.
Visibility to reasoning.
Be able to access data.
I've been reviewing the thinking, seeing
the thought process. Observability in
LLM means application visibility
metrics. Good.
Observability means monitoring,
tracking, and understanding what's
happening inside your LLM application,
not just whether it works. Dashboarding
and alerting. Correct.
Correct.
Observer means being able to see the
work behind the LM, understanding what's
going on. But nice.
All right. Not bad. Not bad at all. For
me, observability is the key
information that is hidden behind the
black box that is your LLM application.
We send all these calls back to some
API. They do some sort of reasoning
inside of their neural network and we
get these answers back by them guessing
tokens. We need to be able to see the
tool calls, the inputs and the outputs,
the system prompt and the user prompt to
exactly know how our system is solving a
problem or completing a task. As a
result, observability is that view.
Every single interaction collated,
sequenced and organized for us to see
the end toend interaction of an LLM.
Each of these questions can be found by
just having them generate generated
through AI. some of the questions that
are available online. Each of you can
take these questions and practice them
for your next AI first engineer
interview. So again, coding with AI and
building with AI.
Okay, next up is product sense. So
again, product manager and engineer is
becoming the same profession. If that's
the case, we need to make sure that we
have some level of judgment.
How would you roll out an AI coding
workflow to your team?
What framework would you use between
fine-tuning and rag? The ability to
discern exactly what to use when, what
to do to ensure that the quality of what
you're building is correct. Now, in the
gauntlet program, what we like to do is
every single project that we have,
there's a target user. That target user
might be video editors, it might be
social media content creators, it might
be professors, whoever it is, you have
an avatar. You start by understanding
that avatar. You research that avatar.
You understand the problems that they're
facing. You then build out a project
according to their needs. This level of
product sense is super important for any
AI engineer. If AI is able to generate
all of the code in the world for you,
then the discerning factor between you
and everybody else using the same AI
coding agent is going to be how you use
that agent, how you manage that agent,
what you put that agent on, how you
distribute what you built with that
agent. Those are your modes. So having
some level of judgment into exactly what
you're building is really, really
important.
Okay, there are some hard questions. So
these are questions that actual Gauntlet
challengers have gotten when they went
into their interviews. So the way this
works is if you join Gauntlet during
week four, you start interviewing with
our platinum partners and that interview
starts halfway through the program. Then
we try to minimize like the number of
interviews you have to do back and forth
and then you get an offer at the end of
the program. But these are some real
interviews that we have seen some
questions that we have seen in real
interviews across the last cohort. Can
you explain every line of your code? Now
this is a trick question because most of
the time there's no way that an engineer
in like a million line codebase 100,000
line codebase can explain explain every
single line of code. Now, if it's a
green field project, if it's a small
project, that's a different story.
That's pretty straightforward and easy.
But let's say you were taking a
disgusting um brownfield repository, a
bunch of duct tape everywhere. You know,
you're in the filth of that code. Then
it's really hard to say what every
single line of code is doing. But what
is important here is to say this was my
thought process when I was adding this
diff.
This is how AI helped me decide. These
are the things that AI produced. This is
how I verified that code and then this
is what that file is doing. You should
understand at least at the file level
what is going on. Be able to understand
hey at the file level I am manipulating
this data in this way. As a result I'm
getting X Y and Z output.
The another another question that's
often asked and I think the reason what
makes this hard is not enough people
actually plan and practice this question
which is what's your methodology with AI
first development. You really need to be
able to talk through the exact tools
that you use, be able to connect those
tools step by step, and then walk
through what would happen and how you
verify what's going on inside of that
sequence of actions. If you're now
managing or directing these coding
agents, you should be able to explain
exactly what you do at a manner that is
reliable, easy to understand, and um can
be understood by the manager who's
interviewing you on the other side.
Finally, deciding between two different
tools is sometimes difficult. You know,
for for example, we have Lang Chain AI
SDK by Versell, the agents SDK by
Claude, the OpenAI agents SDK. If you're
building an agent, how do you decide
what to use when? You have the the
Google models, Gemma, uh Gemini, you'll
have Anthropic, Opus, Sonnet, you have
OpenAI, all of these models that you can
use, Kimmy, Deepseek, a ton of open
source models. How do you decide what
model you should use when? How do you
manage your tokens? One of the key areas
I look for is when I ask somebody about
their methodology with AI, I always say,
"How do you manage your token spend
across your coding agents?
that sometimes how do you decide to use
the dumber model over the smarter model
when you're building out an agent? What
do you do to decide what model to use
and what framework to use? This is
really important and sort of the best
way to sort of do this is to actually
build. So if you take nothing away from
what I'm trying to tell you right now,
it's this that you have to build real
projects in these real areas, rag,
agents, graphs, and evals. And you have
to make sure that you know how to wield
your coding agent really, really well.
Okay. The mindset that wins is you need
to have a methodology that you can
articulate. You need to take ownership
that hey, you are using AI, but you
understand how that AI is doing work.
You can verify its output and you are
confident that you can wield it where
wield it well. You you can explain
tradeoffs not just implement them.
Meaning you have a higher level
understanding of architecture system
thinking and system design. You treat
evals as engineering fundamentals like
regression tests or scores on top of
something you're building. You're
adaptive. You understand that things are
changing. Workflows are changing. The
way we do work is fundamentally
changing. you understand that hey I can
move with the times
if you are interviewing for an AI first
engineer these are the things to keep in
mind.
All right the one thing I want to leave
you with at the end of this lecture
about 45 minutes in now before we start
Q&A is this final checklist. This
checklist is exactly what I would do
before I walk into an interview for an
AI engineering role. Can you narrate
your AI coding workflow step by step
without notes? That means out loud,
slowly, clearly, and so that someone can
understand like a recipe exactly what
you do. Can you explain every file in
the projects that you've added to your
portfolio? Doesn't have to be lines. It
could be the file itself. What is the
purpose of every single file? What are
we trying to get at? And what are we
trying to do in this structure of this
repository? Can you talk through rag,
agents, graphs, and evals coherently?
That doesn't mean you have to be perfect
in these areas. You have to understand
them at a certain level and be able to
showcase maybe a project in one or two
of those categories. Do you know what an
observability platform is? Langmith or
Langfuse? Can you walk through how you
use observability in your LLM
applications? Can you describe what an
eval is and your eval methodology? how
you went from just this basic LLM
application to the complete eval suite
with an agent. Have you practiced how
you use cloud code out loud? Do you have
a clear answer to how you stay ahead in
in the world of AI? Don't just say X.
You know, everybody just says X. No.
What do you do specifically to make sure
you can discern what is a real event in
AI and what is just another uh spammy
headline?
Are you ready to decide on a product
decision, not just the technical one? Do
you have some level of product judgment
or the ability to showcase your product
judgment out loud? So, this is what I
would take away from exactly what was
given in this class so far. Hopefully,
you can take this checklist, pick it up,
and then use it in your next interview.
All right.
Excuse me. We're going to start Q&A now.
It's about 45 minutes into class
and what I'm going to do for Q&A is I'm
going to have the team highlight some
questions here on my phone for me to
answer and then we'll also go into some
of the questions you've been asking over
and over again inside of the Zoom chat.
Now, if any of you are interested in
Gauntlet AI, we do have a cohort
starting on April 27th. Gauntlet AI is a
10-week accelerator that is completely
free. We don't charge anything. There's
no clawbacks. There's no tuition. We
don't charge for food. Nothing at all.
You can you can join this program for
free and be an AI engineer on the other
side. And we only get paid is if you get
placed. This has never happened before
in the world of education. Every single
time you have to give tuition upfront,
you have to pay for things upfront.
Gauntlet doesn't charge you anything and
it never will. There's no ISA. There's
nothing. All you have to do is
participate and be involved. and we will
only make money when we place you on the
other side. So, Gauntlet AI, if you want
to check us out, it's
gauntletai.com/apply.
All right, what are some questions we're
getting?
Okay, first question is from Alicia,
which is, "What are some good ways to
stay in control of codebase if you're
using AI to code using a tech stack that
is new to you?" Go learn the tech stack
first.
Uh it doesn't have to be you don't have
to learn a text stack end to end. It
could be like a three-hour window. It
could be a 2-hour window where you take
a step back and you understand the
underlying principles. If you're already
good in one coding language, for
example, you can pretty much translate
to another coding language the same
principles and concepts. But it's
important for you to take some time and
fully understand exactly what you're
building. And for that reason, I would
take two to three hours, take a step
back and actually understand everything
you're doing. Once you do that, then you
can say, I'm going to go back into the
coding agent and continue coding in the
language I would like. So that is my
recommendation. I say this to gauntlet
students as well. What I like to do is
have them take a step back, spend 2 to
four hours actually learning it. This
could be, I don't know, C, React,
whatever. And once they are more
familiar with it, they can add a skill
associated with that new language and
then continue coding with the coding
agent.
>> Another question from Anoop is how do
you handle the temptation to tell the AI
to just do it while building an
application?
you know, uh there's this thing that
happens with Gauntlet students. It's
like, uh they see an error that like you
can see it in the console log and
they're just like, "Hey, there's an
error. Go fix it." I really think that
it's going to be hard to stop that
temptation from actually happening all
the time cuz sometimes even I just want
to kind of rip my coding agent and have
it build something end to end. And I
actually have a lesson on that. That's
called software factory where can you
give a ticket to a coding agent on
exactly what to build and can it just do
it for you but do it for you really well
with good coding standards good good
test suite a nice deployment pipeline
but that's a whole different scenario in
this scenario uh I to stop this
temptation even just walking through the
console having some sort of acceptance
criteria giving it a little bit more
detail is important the goal here is to
make sure
that what you're trying to build is not
you're not wasting tokens on it. Wasting
tokens is going to become one of the key
areas where engineers can actually learn
to excel because in the future the cost
of these tokens is going to skyrocket.
So we want to get really good at
managing these tokens and making sure
that we're not just saying hey go solve
this without more context or details
because if we did give it the context or
details then it would need to do less
thinking and maybe find the error much
quicker. Now, if it's something super
small, yeah, say that. But most of the
time, give it some level of context.
Question from Sean is how much weight is
given to having an active GitHub hugging
face with active repos for you to demo
or like is or HTML dashboards to share,
for example, something to sort of weigh
in on when you bring into an interview.
I think it's super important. I actually
use GitHub as high signal. One of the
best areas for me to find engineers is
like open- source contributions on some
of the top AI projects. So I really like
uh talking through that because what's
happening is the open source
contributions are going to be a nice way
to judge hey is something actually
or is somebody actually have the skills
necessary to build in this era? Do they
understand the the thing different
primitives of this era and are they
actually skilled in what they do? So in
my opinion, GitHub is a very very nice
location to better understand exactly
what to do. I would make sure you have
GitHub contributions. Hugging face maybe
if you're going for an ML role or maybe
like an AI platform role, that's more
important. But uh for an AI first
software engineer, you can actually go
straight and just focus on GitHub.
All right, what other cont uh questions
do we have?
I have a question here from D which is
I've applied to gauntlet multiple times
scored in the 99 percentile crushed the
coding establishment have a portfolio
and I am a Navy veteran where I served
in most of the technical role in the
entire military now leaving active duty
would love to know any insights into
another I can pursue to get a spot into
the next gauntlet cohort I deeply
believe I would excel in every capacity.
Okay, so we have Gauntlet for America,
which I think is perfect for you,
especially coming from the Navy
background. Um, right now we have over
20 students in Gauntlet for America who
are going to serve um as engineers in
the IRS and the Department of Treasury.
So I think we are now partnering with
many civilian government organizations
and with your background, your ability
and your application that is going to be
a really nice location for you to excel.
So I would put in the gauntlet
application for cohort 5 uh and you'd be
automatically considered for both.
for applying to Gauntlet AI. What would
you recommend for someone who scored a 4
to3 on the CCAT is currently building
but has weak formal engineering
experience? Great question here, Chris.
We do have a wonderkin program. Our
wonderkin program is essentially for
those who don't have 3 years of
experience but still want to be exposed
to the gauntlet program. Uh for those to
qualify under the wonderkin program,
it's the level of project that you can
send over to our admissions team. So we
have you submit sometimes your GitHub,
you can fill out your profile, add your
GitHub. What we're looking for is that
you have uh more than usual engineering
and coding ability and you would qualify
underneath the Wonderkin program. Now,
at the same time, uh you can also just
continue down the road, get the
experience, and then apply in a couple
of years. We plan to do Gauntlet for a
long time, so we're not going to go
anywhere.
Jacob is saying, "I would love to hear
your lesson and insight on letting it
take over your entire end-to-end
software development life cycle. I just
got my agent schedule a cost swapped API
usage and it's somehow I need I need to
heavily optimize. When is the
application cut off for the next
cohort?" The application cut off for the
next cohort is going to be the week
before the 27th. So, it's the graduation
date of the last cohort. I believe it's
the 24th or 25th. So you can you still
have some over three weeks to apply.
Jacob to answer your question directly
on sort of an endto-end implementation.
I like to call it a software factory. Um
I actually have a open source GitHub
repository called minimum viable factory
and I've done a night school session on
this earlier
and the night school session on this
earlier that I did
was basically like how do you set up the
factory? How do you add a product
manager agent and a QA agent and a
deployment agent and connect all the
different platforms and actually build
an endto-end system that can ship
software for you? So, uh to answer your
question directly to give you a more
substantial answer, please check out my
open source project. It's called minimum
viable factory uh and it's on GitHub.
All right. What other questions
from a little document I have here is,
can I say I code in language if AI is
doing the work? The answer is no. The
goal here should be that you guys focus
in on what you have experience in
because you want to make sure that the
things that you're conveying out loud
cover the things that you have actual
experience building in it. Now, if you
did a significant project in them,
that's a different story, but you need
to have tangible proof. Number two, what
AI skill set should we start and acquire
for senior developers out there? The
ability to orchestrate agents and
actually change the way your entire team
is working. So, I did a training uh in
SF just about a week ago on changing the
entire software development life cycle
using spec driven development. If you're
a a staff engineer, uh if you're an
engineering manager, you should be
thinking about how to restructure your
work so that your entire team can
benefit from the ability to code much
faster. Think about shared context and
think about the ability to make sure
that everybody across the entire team
can code at the speed uh of the best
engineer. So check out specdriven
development, spec kitty, these are all
on GitHub.
What is the what are the compensation
expectations for AI engineers? 200k is
the full floor or the ceiling. In my
opinion, 200k is the floor. Uh what
happens with AI engineering is we need
less and less engineers that are just
doing day-to-day junior level work and
more engineers who are orchestrating
agents. And you could be orchestrating
agents across many different
organizations across several different
industries. And the thought process
there is even like for example in
gauntlet we have a minimum 200k bar but
based on your experience your skill set
and your ability to lead that could go
really really high. So it is a floor at
200k not a ceiling.
People keep asking this question and I
got multiple texts about it which is
will we have access to this recording
and the slides. The answer is yes. Uh we
are creating a free learn portal. So you
can actually go into the learn portal,
get this entire recording and then the
associated slides.
How much Python knowledge is essential
to hiring partners? I come from a Java
background and have some experience in
Python. This is a great question. Uh
it's not that a specific
coding language is required for certain
partners. It's that it's good to have
that coding language and understand the
primitives and the different concepts
behind that coding language. But the
goal here is that you're able to be
adaptable. Use what you know already to
understand and learn something new. One
of the most amazing parts of being a
Gauntlet graduate is that you understand
how to code with AI, build AI, and learn
with AI.
They're able to learn 10x faster and
say, "Hey, I can put in 10 hours into
learning this skill, use AI to magnify
my usage of that skill, and then as a
result, be better at a concept much
quicker." So the thought process here is
you may not have any Python knowledge or
Java knowledge, whatever it is, but you
want to use what you know already to
then inform what you're working on next
and then use AI as a learning mechanism
to accelerate that.
If your experience is probably 7030
front end and back end, is that seen as
a negative for hiring partners coming
out of Glet? The answer is no. Uh you
need to have core engineering
experience. That's what we're looking
for here at Gauntlet. If that's front
end, back end, that's okay.
Are the partners you have more
established companies or they newer
startups looking for founding engineers,
AI first industry to move fast? There's
a combination. We have uh seed level
startups, series BC startups to publicly
traded companies. We have PE firms, we
have um conglomerates, we have huge uh
multinationals. There's so many
different gauntlet hiring partners and
we try to find the perfect spot for you.
We have a whole team dedicated to
matching you with a role.
Okay, so I think that was my last one
there because I answered the GitHub and
looking face one, but would love to see
more questions.
DevOps and network engineering are
things that you can use to join. We have
multiple DevOps engineers that uh were
in the program.
All right, we're at the hour. So, if
anybody wants to stay on and still ask
some questions, you totally can. But I
want to just say if you have any
questions about Gauntlet, you can go to
gauntleti.com/faq.
If you decide to apply and join us and
uh build with us for over a,000 hours
here at our Austin, Texas HQ, you can do
that by April 27th. Our cohort 5 starts
on April 27th.
Rajiv is asking how many applications do
I get and what's the acceptance rate? I
think we get like 12,000 applications.
Uh the acceptance rate is like 2%.
>> Ash, can you clarify G GFA?
>> GFA. Uh how many applications we get for
GFA?
>> No, just what the program is the
difference between the two.
>> Yes. So we have two programs running
which is our Gauntlet Prime and our GFA
or which is Gauntlet for America.
Gauntlet Prime is to work in the
commercial sector with our private
hiring partnerships. Uh all the
different companies that we partner with
per cohort. And then GFA is our Gauntlet
for America program where we're
partnering with the government. Uh so
different civilian agencies like the IRS
and Treasury to make sure that they get
the engineering talent that they need.
So both of these areas are looking for
talent and we have two different
programs situated uh to make sure that
they get the talent they need.
Chad is asking, "What's the length and
time commitment for Gauntlet?" It is 10
weeks starting April 27th for cohort 5
and it is 80 to 100 hours a week. I am
not joking. If you don't believe me, you
can ask any of our graduates. We follow
all of them on X. It is actually 80 to
100 hours a week. It is full-time. Our
goal is to completely immerse you in
learning. That complete immersion
results in the best engineers in the
world.
There is no remoteon only cohort. I
don't believe in that. So, it's never
going to happen.
We have to have some level of on-site
in-person learning. That is one of the
tenants and a standard here at a
Gauntlet AI that I will never as long as
I work here change. So, every single
program we do has some sort of in-person
portion. For Gauntlet, it is 3 weeks
remote, 7 weeks on-site. For our
corporate training, it's four weeks
remote, two weeks on-site. For our
custom courses, there's always going to
be one week to whatever number of weeks
on site.
>> Any more questions?
>> Ash, sorry, I have one more question
that someone's asking. Um, there's just
some confusion with GFA in general. Can
you talk about how you apply to GFA and
how there's really no difference?
>> Yep, great question. If you want or if
you're interested in Gauntlet Prime or
GFA, which is Gauntlet for America,
there is no different application
process. All you have to do is go on
gauntleti.com/apply.
You can go to the bottom of the page
here and you can click I'm ready to
apply. Now, this application that you
fill out is for GFA and for G Prime and
makes you a contender for both of those
programs. So, if you would like to join
any of those programs, please apply now.
Jordan's asking, "Have you thought about
creating a sort of transfer portal that
would allow previous grads who have been
working for a certain amount of time to
level up through hiring partners who
might have someone?" Not really, Jordan.
Um, I want to make sure that
the standard I held for all of the
cohorts of gauntlet so far is the same
standard for everybody. So, if everybody
put in 1,000 hours, um, I think I'm
going to make it fair by saying
everybody in the future also has to put
in 1,000 hours.
As someone who is in sales and doesn't
code, it seems like I can use a lot of
these core values you discussed to build
my own AI tools. Where would you
recommend I spend my time learning
something in that area? Great question,
Anthony. I just ran a go to market sales
and marketing training and the main area
you should focus your time on is claude
co-work and building skills on cloud
co-work scheduling those skills and then
connecting all the different
applications you use. So it might be
your CRM might be your enrichment
platform might be your email or your
calendar. What happens is when you
connect all these tools to a single um
app like co-work and then you add skills
on top which break down your domain
expertise in sales, they do a brilliant
job of pretty much automating all your
grunt work.
All right, I think Are we there Tom
Sunny?
>> Yeah, we're good. This has been amazing.
Um, there's someone actually raising
their hand. Do you want to We want them
to talk.
>> Sure. Who's raising their hand?
>> Let me I'm going to make Let them come
off mute.
>> Okay.
>> All right. Wang, you're on.
>> Hello. You guys hear me? Okay.
>> Yes.
>> Oh, okay. Sorry, I'm not expecting you
guys.
Okay. So, I'm Yeah, actually I'm very uh
interested in this program. So, sorry I
I missed the first part. How much cost
per week and uh and the location wise
where you guys located? So, I just
trying to see that.
>> Yeah, we're located in Austin, Texas.
So, the program is three weeks remote,
seven weeks on site. Uh and it's and
it's completely free. So, we cover your
tuition, your food, your laundry, your
flights, your everything. The program is
completely free. The way we the way we
sort of make money on our side is if we
place you at a company, we get a
recruiting placement fee. So, we're like
a recruiting firm and a training center.
>> Okay. Okay. Yeah, I think I'm going to
sign up. So
>> yeah, please do
>> because yeah I so I I I I started with
data migration engineer in Java and
>> and then later on add the devop and the
platform on AWS and
>> yeah the last one year I added AI so I
trying to go further go go deeper into
AI because I work for dental office I
built up a AI agent for them
>> so I trying to go a little bit further
like
go a little bit deeper
rather than
>> Oh, yeah.
Lang, we would we would love to have
you. Please apply someone of your
caliber. You do a great job.
>> Okay. Thank you so much.
>> Of course. Um questions in the chat. Is
the Oh, Anthony, you're asking if the
marketing class is online. It is not,
but I can make it one of the night
school sessions. So, Tom and Sunny,
we're going to have a go to market
session for night school coming up.
Um
Neil's asking who pays the fee, the
student or the hiring company? And how
much is the fee? Neil, the hiring
companies pay the fees. So we are
recruiting firm, right? So after we
train you, we place you and then we
charge 25% of first year salary.
It's like pretty standard recruiting
fee.
Uh Anup is saying, "Silly question. If
you could only use
uh sorry I just lost that question. If
you could only use one AI model for
everything, which one would you pick?
The cheapest one, which is a
controversial question, but the answer
as a CTO, I would pick the cheapest one.
Um Verun is saying, "Seven weeks in
Austin. If I live in Austin, do I have
to move to your location or can I
commute?" You can commute, my friend.
All right, I'm going to call it there,
guys. It was great having you join us
for night school. Gauntlet AI is trying
to retrain the entire workforce for
what's coming in the AI era, and it's
going to take us a long time to change
the way that we actually think about
work. If you like night school, if you
think night school gave you value,
please share night school with somebody
else. have them join night school next
week because I'll be doing this for a
long time and my goal is to provide you
with value and if you're getting value,
please share that across the board.
Thank you again for your time. If you're
interested in applying to Gauntletai
cohort 5, the cohort starts on April
27th and you can go to
gauntletai.com/apply
to do so. Thank you for your time and
thank you for all the questions and
thank you to my amazing staff for
helping facilitate everything. Thank
you. Have a good day. Thank you
everybody.